/* 
  This module contains 50 questions about me
*/

const questions = [
  {
    question: `What is Bharati's favorite season?\n
    a. Autumn
    b. Summer
    c. Winter
    d. Rainy`,
    answer: 'b'
  },

  {
    question: `Who is Bharati's favorite author?\n
    a. Dan Brown
    b. J.K. Rowling
    c. Sarah J Maas
    d. Rick Riordan`,
    answer: 'a'
  },

  {
    question: `What does Bharati do when she is bored?\n
    a. Read Books
    b. Watch Movies or T.V. Series
    c. Sleep
    d. Go Jogging`,
    answer: 'd'
  },

  {
    question: `What app does Bharati use most often??\n
    a. Instagram
    b. Twitter
    c. Discord
    d. WhatsApp`,
    answer: 'c'
  },

  {
    question: `What kind of superpower would Bharati like to poses?\n
    a. Telepathy
    b. Super Speed
    c. Flying
    d. Teleportation`,
    answer: 'd'
  },

  {
    question: `What is Bharati's favorite YouTuber??\n
    a. Traversy Media
    b. Tanay Pratap
    c. freeCodeCamp
    d. She does not watch YouTube`,
    answer: 'c'
  },

  {
    question: `What is Bharati's favorite movie?\n
    a. Avenger's Endgame
    b. 3 Idiots
    c. Pursuit of Happyness
    d. The Karate Kid`,
    answer: 'c'
  },

  {
    question: `How many schools have Bharati gone to since kindergarten?\n
    a. 7
    b. 6
    c. 5
    d. 4`,
    answer: 'b'
  },

  {
    question: `What is Bharati's favorite ice cream flavor?\n
    a. Vanilla
    b. Strawberry
    c. Chocoloate
    d. Butterscotch`,
    answer: 'a'
  },

  {
    question: `What is the biggest turn of for Bharati?\n
    a. Dishonesty
    b. Cursing
    c. Pretense
    d. Ignorance`,
    answer: 'c'
  }  
];


module.exports = {questions};